<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<addons>
  <addon id="repository.rouzax" name="Rouzax Repository" version="1.0.0" provider-name="Rouzax">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="21.0.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Rouzax Repository">
      <dir>
        <info compressed="false">https://rouzax.github.io/repository.rouzax/zips/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://rouzax.github.io/repository.rouzax/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://rouzax.github.io/repository.rouzax/zips/</datadir>
      </dir>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en_GB">Rouzax Kodi Addons</summary>
      <description lang="en_GB">Install and update Rouzax addons: EasyMovie, EasyTV, and QuickList.</description>
      <assets>
        <icon>icon.png</icon>
      </assets>
      <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
      <source>https://github.com/Rouzax/repository.rouzax</source>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.easymovie" name="EasyMovie" version="1.0.1" provider-name="Rouzax">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.1" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
      <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en_GB">Simplify movie night</summary>
      <description lang="en_GB">EasyMovie helps you pick movies for movie night. Answer a few questions (genre, rating, runtime) and get a curated random selection from your library. Supports movie set awareness, multiple viewing modes, and playlist generation.</description>
      <assets>
        <icon>icon.png</icon>
      </assets>
      <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
      <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=385063</forum>
      <website>https://rouzax.github.io/script.easymovie/</website>
      <source>https://github.com/Rouzax/script.easymovie</source>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <news>
v1.0.1 (2026-04-27)
- Resume now actually picks up where you left off
- Resumed playback starts about 10 seconds before the saved point so you catch the context
    </news>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.easytv" name="EasyTV" version="1.5.2" provider-name="Rouzax">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.1" />
      <import addon="script.module.pymysql" version="1.1.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
      <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en_GB">No scrolling. No deciding. Just watching.</summary>
      <description lang="en_GB">Tired of scrolling through your library wondering what to watch? EasyTV handles it. It tracks your shows and always knows your next episode. When you're ready for something new, it'll suggest a show you haven't started. Throw in some movies if you want. Just sit down, press play, and enjoy. Built for Kodi 21+.</description>
      <language />
      <platform>all</platform>
      <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
      <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=383902</forum>
      <website>https://rouzax.github.io/script.easytv/</website>
      <source>https://github.com/Rouzax/script.easytv</source>
      <news>v1.5.2 (2026-05-05)
- Next-episode and missed-episode dialogs redesigned with clearer text and "Watch Next" / "Skip" buttons, matching EasyMovie's pattern.
- Multi-instance sync: shows with new episodes from other Kodi instances now appear in Browse mode without needing a library scan; resume progress and watched state stay current too.
- Clone addons now properly connect to the shared sync database; existing clones will prompt for a mandatory update.
- Browse view show artwork no longer disappears after a partial load; the cache flag self-heals on the next launch.
- "Now Playing" notification now shows the full show title even when the title contains commas.
- Documentation site rebuilt page by page with refreshed screenshots and clearer settings descriptions.</news>
      <assets>
        <icon>icon.png</icon>
        <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
      </assets>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="script.quicklist" name="QuickList" version="1.0.0" provider-name="Rouzax">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="main.py" />
    <extension point="kodi.context.item">
      <menu id="kodi.core.main">
        <item library="main.py">
          <label>$ADDON[script.quicklist 32000]</label>
          <visible>Container.Content(tvshows)</visible>
        </item>
      </menu>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <platform>all</platform>
      <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
      <website>https://github.com/Rouzax/script.quicklist</website>
      <source>https://github.com/Rouzax/script.quicklist</source>
      <summary lang="en_GB">Quickly add or remove TV shows from smart playlists</summary>
      <description lang="en_GB">QuickList adds a context menu item to TV shows that lets you manage which smart playlists they belong to. Select multiple playlists at once with a simple checkbox dialog.</description>
      <news>v1.0.0 (2026-01-24)
- Initial release
- Right-click TV shows to manage playlist membership
- Multi-select dialog for adding/removing from multiple playlists
- Configure which playlists appear via settings</news>
      <assets>
        <icon>icon.jpg</icon>
      </assets>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon id="service.chapternotify" name="Chapter Notify" version="0.7.2" provider-name="Rouzax">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.1" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
      <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en_GB">Show chapter notifications during video playback</summary>
      <description lang="en_GB">Displays a styled overlay notification when a new chapter starts playing in videos from configured library folders. Designed for concert recordings and festival DJ sets with named chapters (Artist - Track [Label]). Perfect companion to CrateDigger, which embeds chapter markers from 1001Tracklists.</description>
      <language />
      <platform>all</platform>
      <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
      <source>https://github.com/Rouzax/service.chapternotify</source>
      <news>v0.7.2 (2026-04-15)
- Fixed festival set overlays not showing the full Artist / Track / Label layout for CrateDig MKV files
- Overlay now reads track info from the MKV Tags section directly, which is where CrateDig stores it
- Title-based matching ensures tags are found even when chapter UIDs do not link correctly
- Accent separator line now stays visible in floating text mode
- Opacity setting is now clamped to a valid range

v0.7.1 (2026-04-14)
- Fixed festival set overlays showing only the raw track title instead of the full Artist / Track / Label layout
- Chapter Notify now reads chapter names directly from the MKV file, picking the English-language display string that CrateDig embeds alongside the plain title entry

v0.7.0 (2026-04-09)
- Added "Show record label" setting so the overlay can hide the record label line on demand
- Overlay now picks panel height to match its content: 3-line, 2-line, or single-line
- Raw chapters that do not match the "Artist - Track [Label]" format render as a clean centered single line instead of an awkward partial 3-line box
- Fixed the historical reversed labeling: the top row in the overlay now correctly says "Track:" (was internally swapped in v0.5.0 through v0.6.0)

v0.6.0 (2026-04-08)
- Added Manual and Both trigger modes - the chapter overlay can now be summoned on demand by pressing a configurable key during playback
- Added Trigger settings group with Mode, Trigger key (free-form text input), and Remove keymap binding action
- Manual trigger bypasses the library path filter, so chapter info can be summoned on any media that has chapters
- Each press of the trigger key always shows or replaces the overlay for visible feedback. To dismiss manually, press any other key
- Default trigger_mode is Auto so existing v0.5.1 behavior is preserved on upgrade

v0.5.1 (2026-04-07)
- Fixed text descenders overlapping the accent separator line
- Improved vertical spacing between all text lines
    </news>
      <assets>
        <icon>icon.png</icon>
      </assets>
    </extension>
  </addon>
</addons>

